# **MAITRAY SUTHAR**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & SOFTWARE SOLUTION PROVIDER

+918866194206

maitraysuthar@gmail.com



--

 $-\Box$ 

--

maitraysuthar.github.io/portfolio/

## **PROFILE**

More than 5+ years of experience of software engineering, implementing leading, and launching software products. Skilled in agile processes, backend, frontend, and web development, object-oriented and functional programming. Well suited for the industry and bringing ideas to life.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER (PHP)**

FEB 2018 - Present

Cygnet Infotech. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN Roles and Responsibilities:

- Web Development with PHP and React, Angular, Vue.
- API Development with PHP Laravel, Nodejs.
- Project deploy (Amazon EC2, cPanel). Worked with Docker.
- Teamwork with QA and BA. Small team management.
- Test-driven development.
- Project & Client Handling. Successfully deployed several projects.

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER (PHP)**

JUN 2016 - FEB 2018

Estatic Infotech. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Web Development with PHP and Angular 2+.
- API Development with PHP Laravel.
- Teamwork with QA and BA. Test-driven development.
- Project & Client Handling.
- Successfully deployed several projects.
- Project deployment (Amazon EC2 Instance, C Panel)

#### **PHP DEVELOPER**

JUN 2013 - OCT 2014

Steamlite Pvt Ltd. Ahmedabad, Gujarat, IN

Roles and Responsibilities:

Web Development with PHP and JQuery.

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: 28-05-1993. Marital Status: Single.

Languages: English (Proficient), Hindi (Fluent) Gujarati (Native).

#### **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING** 2013 - 2016

**INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY** Gujarat Technological University

DIPLOMA OF ENGINEERING 2010 - 2013

**INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY** 

Gujarat Technological University

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript

HTML / CSS

Pvthon MySQL

MongoDB

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

**Problem Solving** 

Adaptability

Team Leading

### TECH SKILLS

**Proficient:** React JS, Laravel, Angular, Node JS, Express JS, Vue JS, Codeigniter, REST API. Payment Gateways, Chat,

Socket.

Basic: Diango, Yii2, Web design, React